

# MONICA **BARTHA**

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

# CONTACT

- +39 328 082 7061
- barthamonica@gmail.com
- monicab.dev

## **SOCIAL MEDIA**

- LinkedIn: monica-bartha
- Github: MonicaBartha
- Behance monica bartha

#### **LANGUAGES**

**ROMANIAN ENGLISH SPANISH ITALIAN** 

## **HOBBIES & INTERESTS**

Serials Music Trekkina Cooking Travel Nature Gym **Books Coffee Summer** Yoga History **Udemy** Events

# **ABOUT ME**

I am front-end developer from Romania. I graduate Laboratoria Bootcamp from Chile, speciality Front-end web developer and now I am open for new work opportunities. My apps are developed in React.Js, Javascript, HTML5, CSS3 and Node JS, using Agile Methodology.

In my work experience, I obtained an eye for detail and appreciation for design, as well as working with colleagues succesfully.



#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### > FREELANCE WEB DEVELOPER

FFR 2018 - OCT 2019

As freelance web developer, I create responsive websites using WordPress, Avada Theme and plugins. I am able to o er a complete product that includes a clean design, development and digital marketing as required (SEO, Google Ads, social media).

#### > WEB DEVELOPER

IUNE 2016 - FEB 2018

At Visual Edge digital agency from Romania. I created WordPress websites by layout design previously created in Photoshop. Also, I implemented Search Engine Optimization and maintenance.



# **PROJECTS**

- > MOOV web app dedicated to people with reduced mobility React | Here Technologies APIs | Single Page App | Mobile first
- > **BURGER QUEEN** restaurant order management web app React | Single Page Application | Tablet first
- > FINGER FOOD social network to find gourmet food Vanilla Javascript | Single Page Application | Firebase | Mobile first



## **EDUCATION**

## > LABORATORIA CHILE

OCT 2019 - MAY 2020

Responsability and compromise

Laboratoria Bootcamp: projects developed using agile methodology, Javascript, React, collaborative Git, testing, Firebase, Figma.

#### > VASILE GOLDIS WESTERN UNIVERSITY OF ARAD 2009 - 2013

Romania; Specialization: Law; Duration: 4 years; Bachelor thesis in Political Sciences: "The rule of law and democracy"



CSS3

## SKILLS

Testing

TECHNICAL SKILLS			SOFT SKILLS
lavaaanint	Viewal Chudia	Dhatashan	Dlamainaina "

Planning using Trello Visual Studio Javascript Photoshop React Firebase Figma Adaptability to changes HTML5 Git & GitHub SEO Collaborative work

WordPress